English Transcript Version Date: 2016-0326
ETVD: 2016-0326 NlTransl MV13-10-2016
You have to put My Feet into your heart.
Plaats Mijn Voeten in jullie hart.
Just My Feet into your heart.
Alleen Mijn Voeten in jullie hart.
Because photo, face, everything might be an illusion.
Want de foto, een gezicht, alles zou een illusie kunnen zijn
Might be, by seeing My Face you do not get over your barriers.
Misschien geraken jullie niet over jullie grenzen door mijn gezicht te zien.
To say, “I must see Mother. I must do this.
Om te zeggen: "ik moet Moeder zien. Ik moet dit doen.
Mother must come to my house. She must have food at my place.
Moeder moet naar mijn huis komen. Ze moet bij mij thuis eten.
She must visit my home.” All this is so stupid.
Ze moet mijn huis bezoeken." Dat is allemaal zo dom.
I cannot understand what’s the matter with these people.
Ik kan niet begrijpen wat er mis is met deze mensen.
“Mother, please come in my heart.
Moeder, kom alstublieft in mijn hart
Let me clean my heart so that You are there.
Laat mij mijn hart zuiveren zodat U daar bent
Put Your Feet into my heart.
Plaats Uw voeten in mijn hart
Let Your Feet be worshipped in my heart.
Laat Uw voeten in mijn hart vereerd worden
Let me not be in delusion.
Laat me niet in waanbeelden blijven
Take me away from illusions.
Haal me weg uit de illusies
Keep me in reality.
Hou me in de realiteit
Take away the sheen of superficiality.
Neem de schijn van oppervlakkigheid weg
Let me enjoy Your Feet in my heart.
Laat me genieten van Uw voeten in mijn hart
Let me see Your Feet in my heart.”
Laat me Uw voeten in mijn hart zien